KANPICHCHA NOKDAM

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Mobile: +66 645454615 Location: Bangkok, Thailand

E-mail:

kanpichcha.nokdam@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kanpichcha-nokdam/

Github:

https://github.com/kanpizza1150

EDUCATION

Christ University

2016 - 2019, Bangalore, India **Bachelor of Computer Application**

SKILL

Languages: ECMAScript (ES6), JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, HTML5, CSS, PostgreSQL, GraphQL Libraries/APIS: React, Next.js, Node.js, NestJS, REST APIs

Tools: Git, NPM, Jira

Paradigms: Responsive Web Design (RWD), Scrum, Agile Other: Mobile First, Front-end Development, Unit testing

LANGUAGE

Thai: Native

English: Proficient

PROFILE

An adaptive Frontend Developer with 2+ years of experience in building and maintaining web apps. Proficient in CSS, HTML, Javascript using ReactJS library with typescript. Experience with NestJS and PostgreSQL. Seeking challenges and opportunities that will enhance self-development. Keen on exploring new areas in technology.

EMPLOYMENT

Sertis / Software Engineering

July 2019 - July 2021 (2y), Bangkok, Thailand

- Work together with a multidisciplinary team with other professionals such as the project manager and UX/UI designer to understand the requirements.
- Provide constructive feedback to the UI design on any possible product improvement.
- Building web applications using ReactJS framework and Redux as state management along with unit testing with Jest and React Testing Library.
- Experience with RESTful API integrations, SSO SAML login integration.
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews.

Onework / Front-End Developer

August 2021 - PRESENT, Bangkok, Thailand

- Building web applications with Next.js and React (typescript).
- Implementing APIs Rest With Nest.js and PostgreSQL.
- Wrapping REST APIs in GraphQL.
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews.

EXPERIENCE

Remedy Coffee (Front-End Web development)

https://www.remedy.coffee/

Online Ordering platform(web app) for a Coffee Shop.

- Designing UX/UI for mobile-first web application.
- Implementing with React (typescript).